iSpring fans welcome to another
iSpring粉丝欢迎来到另一个
installment of spring tips in this
在此安装弹簧提示
installment we're gonna take a sort of a
分期付款，我们将采取一种
different look a different approach
不同的外观不同的方法
we're gonna talk about it something that
我们要谈论的是
you know probably we wouldn't have
你知道我们可能不会
normally talked about you wouldn't
通常说到你不会
normally think about doing this with uh
通常考虑用呃做
with spring but it's an option and it
春天，但这是一个选择，
works and I thought it was quite an
工作，我认为这是一个相当
interesting mix so we're gonna do it
有趣的混合，所以我们要去做
we're gonna talk about how to integrate
我们将要讨论如何整合
spring better say spring boot with
春天最好说春天引导与
JavaFX now you ask why JavaFX well
JavaFX现在您问为什么JavaFX很好
there's a few reasons first of all when
首先有几个原因
JavaFX first came out java fix of course
JavaFX当然首先出现了Java修复
for those of you aren't aren't know is a
因为你们中的那些不是
is a component library it's a UI
是一个组件库，它是一个UI
framework it's a UI toolkit based on
框架，它是一个基于
this idea of a stage or as I'm sorry a
这个阶段的想法，或者我很抱歉
scene and a scene has a components
场景和场景具有组成部分
inside of it but it's also got this
在里面，但它也有这个
sense of a timeline so you can use it to
时间轴的意义，因此您可以使用它来
do really interesting things you know
做一些有趣的事情
like animation right and it technically
像动画一样，从技术上讲
it's a it's a it's a sort of a more
这是一个更多
advanced more interesting application
高级更有趣的应用程序
development technology than something
开发技术比什么
like for example base swing recently in
例如最近在
Java 11 it has been divorced from the
Java 11已脱离
core Java sort of runtime so it's no
Java核心运行时，所以不是
longer bundled it's actually now
捆绑在一起实际上是现在
separate available as maven dependencies
单独可用作为maven依赖项
and as a result it's got a whole new
结果，它有了一个全新的
life or and it can move independent of
生活或它可以独立于
the release cadence of the of the JDK
JDK的发布节奏
himself and there's this you know I I've
他自己，这就是你，我知道我
just seen over the years a lot of really
多年来看到的很多
interesting use cases people use it to
人们用它来有趣的用例
do visualizations right you see all
对所有内容进行可视化处理
these really great demos with respect to
这些真的很棒的演示
medical imaging or you know astronomy
医学影像或天文学
and and general physics simulations all
和一般物理模拟
these kinds of really interesting things
这些非常有趣的事情
that I think really really speak to why
我认为我真的在说为什么
you would want to use this right it's a
您将要使用此权限，这是一个
you can produce some very very beautiful
你可以产生一些非常非常美丽的
things you know multimedia rich user
您知道的多媒体富用户
interfaces and in order for that to work
接口并为了使其正常工作
these things need to talk to two
这些事情需要和两个人谈谈
services they need to talk to backends
他们需要与后端对话的服务
and here especially in light of the
而这里特别是鉴于
reactive programming paradigm that
反应式编程范式
spring
弹簧
framework five and all the technologies
框架五和所有技术
that build upon its support we have a
依靠它的支持，我们有一个
really interesting option right now is
现在真正有趣的选择是
spring is a natural link it's a provides
春天是自然的联系
a for example a reactive web client for
例如，一个用于
HTTP based services and a WebSocket
基于HTTP的服务和WebSocket
client I mean these things are a natural
客户，我是说这些东西是自然的
match for client-side applications you
匹配您的客户端应用程序
can use the spring framework web support
可以使用Spring Framework 的web支持
the reactive web support in a client
客户端中的反应式Web支持
application and just tell it not to run
应用程序，只是告诉它不要运行
a web server and there you go you have
一个Web服务器，然后您就可以拥有
access to all these very convenient
获得所有这些非常方便
things like the like the web client for
像网络客户端这样的事情
example so while we're not going to talk
例如，所以当我们不谈论
about the reactive web client today
关于今天的响应式Web客户端
specifically we're going to talk about
特别是我们要谈论的是
how to build a a just a utterly boring
如何建立一个完全无聊的
stock standard sort of JavaFX
标准标准的JavaFX
application and how to how to hoist up a
应用程序以及如何举起
spring application context in the sort
春天的应用程序上下文
of lifecycle of a Java FX application so
Java FX应用程序的生命周期
let's do that let's go to our normal
让我们做到这一点，让我们回到正常状态
go-to spot we'll go to start that spring
去那个地方，我们将在那个春天开始
that IO here and we're just gonna build
IO在这里，我们将建立
a new application just as we always -
一如既往的新应用-
we're gonna build a simple Java FX
我们将构建一个简单的Java FX
okay so Java FX and you know as you can
好吧，Java FX和您就可以知道
imagine when you use Lombok maybe
想像一下您何时使用龙目岛
bringing the reactive web support I'm
带来我的反应式网络支持
gonna use 2.1 Oh
要用2.1哦
RFC 1 I'm gonna switch the whole version
RFC 1我要切换整个版本
and give myself Java 11 I'm running Java
给自己Java 11我正在运行Java
11 you can use Java you can use earlier
11.可以使用Java，可以更早使用
versions of Java but those versions will
Java版本，但这些版本将
include Java effects so in theory there
包括Java效果，所以理论上讲
might be there might have been some
可能有可能有一些
drift between what's possible and open
在可能与开放之间漂移
Java FX open jfx which is what I'm gonna
Java FX open jfx这就是我要去的
use here versus what's core and bundled
在这里使用与核心和捆绑在一起
into the JVM into the Java Runtime and
进入JVM进入Java Runtime并
by the way that Java effects hasn't it's
顺便说一下Java效果不是
not a part of the spec it's never been
不是规范的一部分，从来没有
you know consistently deployed across
您知道始终跨
all Java runtimes anyway right it's a I
反正所有Java运行时都是I
know I know that for example Oracle JDK
知道我知道例如Oracle JDK
has had top effects but that's not
产生了最佳效果，但事实并非如此
necessarily true of open JDK for example
例如，对于开放式JDK必然如此
so so it's nice that these things are
所以这些东西很好
now separate that you can choose to
现在分开，您可以选择
install them if you like and there's no
如果需要，请安装它们，没有
worries but how it works and also spring
担心，但它如何工作，还会弹跳
has this really nice convenient sort of
有这种非常好用的便利
so call
所以打电话
fat jar mechanism for distribution that
胖子罐子的分配机制
I think is a nice fit when you want to
我想很适合
build simple but useful client-side
构建简单但有用的客户端
applications in a previous installment
上一期中的应用程序
of spring tips we looked at how to build
春天的技巧，我们看了如何建立
spring shell based CLI applications so
基于Spring Shell的CLI应用程序
consider this they sort of you know
考虑一下，他们有点你知道
windows for workgroups version of that
Windows的工作组版本
of that discussion right now how do you
现在的讨论中，你如何
build user interfaces with with spring
用spring建立用户界面
and we've done this before we've
而且我们已经做到了
actually looked at a other UI toolkits
实际上看了其他UI工具包
right we've actually looked at a web
对，我们实际上已经看过网络了
frameworks for example in the in
框架，例如
previous installment so this isn't
以前的分期付款，所以这不是
entirely out of the blue okay let's see
完全出乎意料好吧，让我们看看
we're gonna go start up our application
我们将要启动我们的应用程序
UA JavaFX zip as usual and when that
UA JavaFX zip照常执行，何时执行
spins up we're gonna open it'll open up
旋转起来，我们要打开它会打开
in our in our IDE or trusty IDE here and
在我们的IDE或可信赖的IDE中，
I'm using IntelliJ and again lots of
我正在使用IntelliJ，然后再次使用
good choices here NetBeans in particular
这里特别是NetBeans的不错选择
is a great choice because it has a
是一个不错的选择，因为它具有
really really good you know rock-solid
真的非常好，你知道坚如磐石
integrated support for Java FX IntelliJ
对Java FX IntelliJ的集成支持
at least as far as I know in the
至少据我所知
Ultimate Edition has very good job FX
终极版效果很好
support as well I'm not sure about the
支持以及我不确定
Community Edition but it wouldn't
社区版，但不会
surprise me so you might well might well
让我感到惊讶，所以你可能会很好
check that out ok so first things first
检查一下，所以首先
in order for us to get anywhere with
为了让我们与
this we need well we need we need it out
我们需要它，我们需要它
JavaFX right that's pretty fair so let's
JavaFX对，这很公平，所以让我们
import or rather use a number of
导入或使用一些
libraries here so we're gonna use a Java
库在这里，所以我们要使用Java
FX controls and this will require org
FX控件，这将需要组织
dots open jfx ok and we need to bring in
点打开jfx好的，我们需要引入
the right version which corresponds to
对应的正确版本
11 that's the JDK we're using and I'm
11这就是我们正在使用的JDK，而我
I'm just gonna bring in a number of
我要带一些
things here we don't need them all
这里的事情我们不需要全部
certainly but it's nice to have them so
当然可以，所以很高兴
we want the controls which are the
我们想要的控件是
widgets or at least some of the widgets
小部件或至少某些小部件
and there's a huge ecosystem of
而且有一个巨大的生态系统
third-party widgets controls UI elements
第三方小部件控制UI元素
whatever you want to call them at your
不管你想给他们打电话
disposal at your fingertips and I
唾手可得，我
encourage you to peruse that larger
鼓励你仔细阅读
community because there are some really
社区，因为确实有一些
interesting things that
有趣的事情
upon this we're gonna bring in the
在这一点上，我们将带来
graphics support here we're gonna bring
我们将带来图形支持
in the base support and F XML is the
在基本支持中，F XML是
two-way user interface markup language
双向用户界面标记语言
that supports binding to user interface
支持绑定到用户界面
elements so you can describe your your
元素，以便您可以描述您的
your layout in a static sort of
您的布局是静态的
hierarchical structure and then have
然后有层次结构
those elements mapped to Java objects
这些元素映射到Java对象
and those objects can then be
然后这些对象可以是
manipulated in Java code so you can you
用Java代码进行操作，因此您可以
can do the layout and design in XML
可以用XML进行布局和设计
which is a natural use of XML and then
这是XML的自然用法，然后
articulate the behavior in Java code so
阐明Java代码中的行为，因此
what happens when somebody clicks on the
当有人点击
button or you know when the window loads
按钮，或者您知道窗口何时加载
or whatever okay okay so those are
或其他任何可以的东西
simple maven build and that's it that's
简单的Maven构建，就是这样
really all that we need we have the web
确实我们需要的所有东西都拥有网络
support on a class path but we don't
在课堂上提供支持，但我们不支持
need it so I'm gonna say none right just
需要它，所以我不会说什么就对了
disable the webserver and now we're
禁用网络服务器，现在我们
gonna go to a simple application now
现在要去一个简单的应用程序
there's a little bit of there's a
有一点点
there's a little bit of a problem here
这里有点问题
right there's a little bit of an
右边有一点
impedance between how Java FX wants to
Java FX想要达到的阻抗
work and how spring wants to work spring
工作以及春天如何工作
normally as you can see here is the sort
就像你在这里看到的那样
of front and center it's the thing that
前面和中间的东西
hoists the rest of your application into
将其余的应用程序提升到
existence with Java FX it's not so easy
Java FX的存在并不容易
to do that or rather it's it's the path
做到这一点，或者这就是路径
the path of least resistance is to first
阻力最小的路径是首先
all bootstrap Java effects and then let
所有引导Java效果，然后让
Java fix bootstrap your spring
Java修复引导您的春天
application ok so we're gonna write as
好的应用程序，所以我们要写成
little as we can
尽我们所能
outside of spring but we're gonna write
春天以外，但我们要写
just enough to instantiate an install
仅足以实例化安装
spring and then we're gonna write code
春天，然后我们要编写代码
to integrate the two so that one talks
将两者融合在一起
to the other and so that when for
对方，所以当
example Java FX needs a a reference to a
Java FX示例需要引用一个
controller or a component it looks to
控制器或它要寻找的组件
beans that are being managed by spring
春季管理的豆类
ok so first things first our spring good
好的，首先是我们的春天
application our public static void main
应用我们的公共static void main
is actually going to use the
实际上将使用
the Java fix application class okay so
Java修复应用程序类可以
there you go dot launch and in order for
在那里，您进行点发射，并为了
it to launch it needs a pointer to a
它启动它需要一个指向
class which extends application so I'm
类扩展了应用程序，所以我
gonna call this our Java FX application
将其称为我们的Java FX应用程序
oops
哎呀
yes okay so that let's see it lets just
是的，好，让我们来看一下
call this new class beautiful FX
将此新类称为美丽的FX
application this will be our spring boot
应用程序，这将是我们的春季引导
entry point and it'll have this code as
入口点，它将具有以下代码
well okay and this will be our our
好吧，这将是我们的
actual Java fix application okay so I'm
实际的Java修复应用程序可以，所以我
gonna say extends application and we
要说扩展应用程序，我们
have to implement the minimum required
必须执行最低要求
interface for contract here to get some
合同的接口在这里得到一些
abstract type so we implant start I'm
抽象类型，所以我们开始植入
gonna come back to that in a second and
一会儿再回到
here we'll say that we want
在这里，我们会说我们想要
JavaFX application class to be launched
将启动JavaFX应用程序类
with these arguments and and that's it
这些论点，仅此而已
that's the basic arrangement now now
这是现在的基本安排
you're gonna see that from within our
你会从我们内部看到
Java fix application class we're gonna
Java修复应用程序类
reference beautiful effects application
参考美丽效果应用
so these both need to be public they
所以这些都需要公开
both need to be visible to each other
两者都必须彼此可见
and I find that a bit disappointing it
我觉得有点令人失望
in some examples that you'll see online
在一些您会在线看到的示例中
you'll see that they have the Springwood
你会看到他们有斯普林伍德
application bug static void main the
应用程序错误静态void main
JavaFX launch and the the the you know
JavaFX启动和您所知道的
spring boot stuff all the same code base
spring boot 的东西都是相同的代码库
but for reasons I don't quite understand
但由于某些原因，我不太了解
yet I gather that this somehow checks
但是我收集到这以某种方式检查
that the class that's running in is also
正在运行的类也是
the same one that is the application and
相同的是应用程序和
it does some thing where it looks for a
它在寻找的地方做了一些事情
certain Java module from jigsaw and the
拼图和某些Java模块
JPM JPM it's trying to drum up java
JPM JPM正在尝试鼓吹Java
module system right and once that's
模块系统的权利，一旦
there if it's detected then it
如果检测到那里，那么它
it it needs a certain thing to be
它需要确定的东西
explicitly made available well I'm
明确提供好我
learning this in class path mode there's
在课堂路径模式下学习
no module path so that check seems
没有模块路径，以便检查
arbitrary to me if I'm honest I don't
如果我说实话，我对我很武断
know why it's there and it doesn't
知道为什么它在那里，但它不
really help us at all but but um as a
真的对我们有很大帮助，但作为一个
result I found that if I just tease
结果我发现，如果我只是取笑
these two parts out in just two separate
这两个部分分成两个部分
classes everything just works okay so
上课一切正常，所以
we'll just leave it like that because
我们就这样保留它，因为
you know all told it's certainly a lot
你们都知道这肯定很多
easier than not being able to do what we
比不能做我们要容易
want to do right so okay we have our
想做正确的事，好吧，我们有
chop effects application what is our job
印章效果应用我们的工作是什么
at FX application we're gonna do well it
在FX应用程序上，我们会做得很好
has to boot up boot doesn't it it has to
必须启动启动不是吗
be the thing that hoists spring into
是葫芦涌入的东西
existence and we're gonna do so in terms
存在，我们将用术语
of the application lifecycle so let's
应用程序生命周期的过程，所以让我们
say we have a class a pointer to a
说我们有一个类指向
configurable application context right
可配置的应用程序上下文权限
and there's our context and that context
这是我们的背景，那个背景
is the spring application context that
是Spring应用程序上下文
we're going to initialize when the
我们将在
application the JavaFX application
应用JavaFX应用
springs to life right so let's override
泉水生机勃勃，所以让我们超越
this method in it and in the init method
此方法及其init方法
we're gonna say this dot context equals
我们要说这个点上下文等于
new spring application builder dot
新的Spring应用程序构建器点
sources who does e bootiful FX
谁做外汇的消息来源
application class that initializers
初始化程序的应用程序类
initializer and we're gonna need an
初始值设定项，我们需要一个
initializer and the reason is cuz i want
初始化程序，原因是因为我想要
to programmatically but just to some
以编程方式，但仅对某些
beans okay so we could do this a number
豆好了，所以我们可以做一些
of different ways
不同的方式
but as you'll see since I'm trying to
但正如您所看到的，因为我正在尝试
involve objects that are already created
涉及已经创建的对象
and that exist outside of the spring
而且存在于春天之外
application context we're gonna use the
应用程序上下文，我们将使用
the programmatic bean definition syntax
程序化bean定义语法
is available in spring 5m5 here we can
在5m5春季可用，我们可以
get our parameters but we're gonna get
得到我们的参数，但我们会得到
our parameters from java fix right so
我们的Java参数正确修复了
Java fix already has those parameters we
Java修复程序已经具有这些参数，
already gave it to it so here in order
已经给它了，所以这里按顺序
to make sure that all of spring has
以确保整个春天都有
access to those command-line arguments
访问这些命令行参数
when
什么时候
Passman here and now we need to create
现在，我们需要创建Passman
an application context initializer so
应用程序上下文初始化程序
we've we looked at we looked at this in
我们已经看过了
a previous installment of spring tips
先前的Spring Tips
would have two functional beam
会有两个功能光束
definitions so you might want to review
定义，因此您可能需要查看
that but this is still pretty simple
那个，但这仍然很简单
either way so initializer equals new
无论哪种方式，所以初始化器等于new
application context initializer and here
应用程序上下文初始化器和此处
we're gonna programmatically register a
我们将以编程方式注册一个
few beams army so AC and we're gonna say
几束光束，所以AC，我们要说
AC register a beam now which beam do we
AC现在注册一束光
want well I want to make the application
想要很好，我想申请
itself available for injection and for
本身可用于注射和
reference in other places all say I want
其他地方的参考都说我要
to reference this basically okay I
引用这个基本上可以了
suppose we can do Java effects
假设我们可以做Java效果
application back this it's a little
应用程序回来这有点
easier what else do we want we want the
更容易我们想要什么我们想要的
parameters themselves and again we could
参数本身，我们可以再次
do reference them from the application
从应用程序中引用它们
itself I suppose but let's just make
我想我自己，但让我们
them explicitly available and finally
他们明确可用，最后
want the host services now the host
想要主机服务现在是主机
services provides things like like you
服务提供像您一样的东西
know the ability to resolve references
知道解决引用的能力
relative to code base and to launch
相对于代码库和启动
operating system specific browsers right
特定于操作系统的浏览器
URLs and browsers so very very
URL和浏览器非常非常
convenient thing to have a reference to
方便参考的东西
there's our initializer and we're just
有我们的初始化程序，我们只是
gonna pass that in here so what that's
要在这里传递，那是什么
gonna do is it's gonna say - spring here
要说的是-春天来了
are three beans of type application
是三种类型的应用程序
parameters and host of services in order
参数和服务的主机顺序
to you know in order to - whenever
你知道为了-每当
somebody wants to inject them give them
有人想注射他们给他们
the reference we turn to you from this
我们从中得到的参考
supplier which we're describing in terms
我们用术语描述的供应商
of a lambda all right when that starts
一个lambda开始就好了
up it's gonna run the init method this
它将运行init方法
is a great place to do any kind of work
是做任何工作的好地方
that does not run on the user interface
无法在用户界面上运行
thread so any kind of stuff that you
线程，这样的东西，你
want to do to you know prepare the
想对你做知道的准备
application to begin to load you would
应用程序开始加载你会
do here in this case we're using it as
在这种情况下，我们在这里使用它作为
an enviable place to instantiate spring
一个令人羡慕的实例化春天的地方
and the application
和应用
Texan zone and the converse of that the
德克萨斯州地区与之相反
opposite end of that is the stop
另一端是停止
admitted okay so I'm gonna say stop and
承认还好，所以我要说停下来
here we'll say this dot context up close
在这里，我们将近一点说点环境
and platform Donna exit yeah very good
和平台唐娜退出是的，非常好
now we see this start method the start
现在我们看到这个启动方法
method is pretty useful this is the
方法非常有用，这是
callback that you get when the
当
application is ready right when it's
应用程序准备就绪
ready when it's time to start building
准备开始建造时
up your user interface and you could do
设置您的用户界面，您可以
all that work here but that would be in
所有在这里工作，但那将在
this application class that is not you
这个不是您的应用程序类
know you can't benefit from any
知道你不能从中受益
injection and so on any any of the
注射等等
services that spring provides so what I
春天提供的服务，所以我
like to do here is to to instead publish
我喜欢在这里做的是发布
an event publish the event and the event
一个事件发布事件和事件
I guess we'll just be a let's see a
我想我们只是来看看
stage ready event it's an application
舞台准备事件是一个应用程序
event application context event right
事件应用程序上下文事件权限
and the job is first you know the
首先是你知道的
description the work is very straight
描述工作很直
for going to pass in the stage and we
为了通过舞台，我们
could even be more explicit about that
甚至可以更明确地
we could say okay you know public stage
我们可以说好吧，你知道公众场合
get stage okay
做好舞台
and return this dot sores all right
并返回这个点疮好吧
better suppose they could have just sort
更好地假设他们可以进行排序
of pointed to it but why right we better
指向它，但为什么对，我们更好
get out before they got that okay so I'm
在他们还好之前就出去，所以我
gonna throw that event new stage ready
要把那个事件扔到新的舞台上
event primary stage now all spring
活动主要阶段现在整个春季
components that express an interest in
表达兴趣的组件
listening for this event will be able to
收听此事件将能够
listen to it and initialize the the
听它并初始化
stage or contribute to the stage and
舞台或为舞台做贡献
whenever they want to and they can do so
只要他们愿意，他们就可以这样做
in terms of beans that are managed by by
就由...管理的bean而言
Spring which is good okay so I think
春天很好，所以我想
that's it I think that's enough for that
就这样，我认为就足够了
that's a very very simple sort of
这是非常非常简单的一种
integration there for Java effects and
在那里集成了Java效果和
for for spring now we have we have to
对于现在的春天，我们必须
build something that actually listens to
建立真正听的东西
that event I suppose so let's go back
我想是那个事件，让我们回去
over here in and you know configure the
在这里，您知道配置
application a little bit let's build
应用程序一点，让我们建立
something that actually works with that
与之实际起作用的东西
that stage okay so go here stage
那个阶段好吧，所以去这里阶段
initializer or
初始化器或
let's see application runner I don't
让我们看看我没有的应用程序运行器
know stage listener okay there we go
知道舞台聆听者好吧，我们去了
oh just call that very sort of
哦，只是叫那种
straightforward and this is going to
简单，这将
implement application listener listen
实现应用程序监听器
for the stage ready event influencing
舞台准备事件的影响
this method and there we are there's our
这种方法，我们在那里
there's our callback now we can now we
现在有我们的回调，我们现在可以
can do what everyone and this is a swing
可以做每个人的事，这是一个摇摆
beam after all so let's say add
毕竟光束，所以说添加
component and what we're going to do is
组件，我们要做的是
we're going to build the user interface
我们将构建用户界面
and we're going to do so by giving it a
我们将通过给它一个
title so let's say title or application
标题，所以说标题或应用程序
title and this is the thing I would have
标题，这就是我要的东西
to externalize so I can take advantage
外部化，以便我可以利用
of Springs ability to externalize
弹簧外在化能力
Springs and the properties or message
弹簧和属性或消息
you know resource bundles so I'm gonna
你知道资源包，所以我要
say spring that application UI title and
说春天那个应用程序UI标题和
let's see
让我们来看看
you okay here
你还好吧
alright so there's that now copy and
好了，现在有复制和
paste
糊
okay that was bizarre hopefully this is
好吧，那很奇怪，希望这是
a fixed I've just updated to the latest
我刚刚更新到最新的固定
and greatest Mac OS Mojave so I wonder
和最伟大的Mac OS Mojave，所以我想知道
if that's causing these odd oddness when
如果那引起这些奇怪的奇怪
recording okay back to this okay so
记录好吧回到这好吧
we've got now our Java FX application
我们现在有了我们的Java FX应用程序
and we've got our bootiful application
而且我们有可启动的应用程序
alright so there's that and now we're
好了，就是这样，现在我们
going to process the data and the
将要处理数据和
application properties I'm gonna give it
我要给它的应用程序属性
a title which will clean from here
将从这里清除的标题
follow this beautiful Java Thanks
跟随这个美丽的Java谢谢
alright there's our our basic
好了，这是我们的基本
application and now what I want to do is
应用程序，现在我要做的是
I want to actually you know with this
我真的想知道
stage that we've gotten from this event
我们从这次活动中获得的舞台
when I say stage ready event dot its
当我说舞台准备活动点
stage what I want to do is I want to I
我想做的就是我想要我
want to load my user interface so I
想加载我的用户界面，所以我
don't I could manually programmatically
我不能以编程方式手动
with Java objects build up a user
用Java对象建立用户
interface hierarchy and build up the
接口层次结构并建立
widgets and then you know all that stuff
小部件，然后您知道所有这些东西
in Java code but it's far more useful
用Java代码编写，但它要有用得多
and far more productive
而且生产力更高
especially for sort of forms and
特别是对于某种形式和
analytical type applications like this
像这样的分析型应用
to just do it to you to do it using FX
只是用FX来做
ml all right this is the JavaFX XML
ml好的，这是JavaFX XML
markup language so we're gonna say file
标记语言，所以我们要说文件
UI dot that's XML reload that and we'll
XML的UI点将重新加载该点，我们将
come back to that in a second but for
再过一秒钟再说
now because we want to be able to
现在，因为我们希望能够
reference that we need to have a pointer
我们需要有一个指针的参考
to the resource so private finally doors
对资源如此私密的最后大门
at XML resource of course is an
XML资源当然是
abstraction core spring that allows us
抽象核心弹簧使我们
to to represent things that we
代表我们所要做的事情
which we can do input-output right so
我们可以正确地进行输入输出
classpath /ui f as well okay so you can
classpath / ui f也可以，所以您可以
tell spring to find that resource and
告诉春天找到那个资源，
inject it as a constructor argument for
将其作为构造函数参数注入
us and then we say this dot XML resource
我们，然后我们说这个点XML资源
okay good
好的
and now what we're gonna do is we're
现在我们要做的是
gonna say we want to get the URL so URL
要说我们想获取URL，所以URL
this stuff F XML and I get URL okay so
这个东西是F XML，我可以找到URL，所以
okay now we have our URL that's load the
好的，现在我们的网址已加载
definition so XML loader like that I'm
定义，所以我像这样的XML加载器
gonna say URL dot
要说URL点
oh that's it actually there's pass on
哦，就是这样，实际上已经过去了
URL and then we're gonna use effort to
URL，然后我们将努力
malodorous is that the controller
恶臭的是控制器
factory so the question now is what is
工厂，所以现在的问题是
the F XML gonna do when it needs an
F XML会在需要
object that's been referenced in the F
F中已引用的对象
XML declaration then we'll see what that
XML声明，那么我们将看到
means in a second so for example suppose
例如，以秒为单位
we have a I use interface with a
我们有一个我使用界面
controller type a class that gets
控制器输入要获取的类
involved in the the the sort of
参与那种
functionality the backing functionality
功能支持功能
for a user interface well it has to find
对于用户界面，它必须找到
an object that matches a certain class
符合特定类别的对象
to the contract is here the contract
合同是这里的合同
here is given a class return object well
这里给了一个很好的类返回对象
of course what does that sound like that
当然，那听起来像什么
sounds like a one of those things that
听起来像是那些东西之一
spring could do really well for us so
春天对我们来说真的很好
we're gonna say that we need to point it
我们要说我们需要指出
to the application context right so we
对应用程序上下文的权利，所以我们
can get a reference to that application
可以获取该应用程序的参考
context and we can do that just by
上下文，我们可以做到这一点
injecting it actually right it's just a
实际上注入它只是一个
regular spring mate so I will say
定期的春季伴侣，所以我会说
application context
应用环境
okay already so it's there I'm gonna say
好了，现在我要说了
the turn PC that get beam a class
上课的转身电脑
alrighty now there's our lambda and with
好了，现在有我们的lambda和
that we should be able to load the
我们应该能够加载
application so I'm gonna say load and
应用程序，所以我要说负载和
I'm gonna ask for the parent widget that
我要问父母的小部件
comes back the route widget as they
当他们返回路线小部件时
return by you and we can stash that or
由您返回，我们可以将其藏起来或
we can just use it and what I'm gonna do
我们可以使用它，而我要做什么
here is I'm gonna I'm gonna use it to
这是我要用它来
create a scene
创建一个场景
so you seen passing in the route giving
所以你看到路过
it a width and a height of let's say 600
宽度和高度可以说600
by 600 pixels and then I'm gonna say
600像素，然后我要说
stage that set the scene scene stage
舞台设置场景舞台
that says the title we've got that title
那就是标题，我们已经有了标题
that we've been injected so as we use it
我们已经被注射，以便我们使用它
stage dot set just show right I want to
舞台点集只是显示我想要的
show this stage now alright so there we
现在显示这个阶段，所以我们
go that's our application that's how
这就是我们的应用程序
we're gonna build the user interface we
我们将建立用户界面
still actually haven't built the user
实际还没有建立用户
interface that way so let's do that
以这种方式进行交互，让我们做到这一点
right here and so what we're gonna do is
就在这里，所以我们要做的是
gonna build a user interface one of two
要建立两个用户界面之一
ways we could do this we could use the
我们可以做到的方式，我们可以使用
scene builder which i think is a fine
我认为很好的场景构建器
way to go right so ours is I know ours
正确的方法，所以我们是我们的
couldn't be more trivial so that's
再简单不过了
actually you know we could just drag and
实际上，您知道我们可以拖动并
rule
规则
or here we are so you can see it's
还是我们在这里，所以你可以看到
arguably more efficient just just to do
可以说只是为了做而更有效率
that okay so we want to build a V box
好的，所以我们要建立一个V形盒
and in the box we'll have a button
在框中，我们将有一个按钮
controls
控制项
all right
好吧
and illegal
和非法的
okay now go back to this and we should
好吧，现在回到这一点，我们应该
have a V box although you know I don't
有一个V形盒子，虽然你知道我没有
really know that we need this children
真的知道我们需要这个孩子
element okay
元素还可以
and we need to give our widgets some IDs
我们需要给小部件一些ID
that way we can sort of you know connect
这样我们就可以让您知道连接
them to the user to the Java objects in
它们给用户到Java对象中
the backing controller which we also
支持控制器，我们也
need to specify so we need to specify a
需要指定，所以我们需要指定一个
number of things here so first of all
这里的事情数量如此之多
IDs FX ID button FX ID label alright and
ID FX ID按钮FX ID标签正确和
then with that done we need to specify a
然后，我们需要指定一个
controller so let's go to controller
控制器，所以我们去控制器
here
这里
okay and a controller is just a beam
好吧，控制器只是一束光
that spring is going to involve or that
那个春天将涉及或
JavaFX is gonna involve as I say so that
正如我所说的，JavaFX将涉及到
beam will be you know simple what is
梁会是你知道简单的是什么
this
这个
you know UI simple UI controller alright
你知道UI简单的UI控制器好吗
and it's just a regular spring object
这只是一个普通的弹簧物体
just nothing fancy at all that went
一切都没有幻想
spring we're gonna tell this to delegate
春天，我们要告诉这个委托
to that class that's going to result in
到那个班的结果
a call to the connection factory that
到连接工厂的电话
we've contributed somewhere here the
我们在这里的某个地方
connection they connect controller
连接他们连接控制器
factory that's gonna resolve beans for
工厂将解决豆
us so you know we could arguably make
我们，所以你知道我们可以做
this a little bit more we could name it
这一点我们可以命名
a little bit better application context
更好的应用程序上下文
very good alright so there's our
很好，所以我们有
application and there's our widgets our
应用程序，还有我们的小部件
simple controller and what's gonna
简单的控制器，将会发生什么
happen when this controller gets started
控制器启动时发生
well we have to have a place to stash
好，我们必须有一个藏身之处
these references so let's go ahead and
这些参考资料，让我们继续
build a simple controller using the F
使用F建立一个简单的控制器
XML annotation so go to our simple UI
XML注释，请转到我们的简单UI
controller and our application is gonna
控制器，我们的应用程序将
be the trigger list of trivial right
成为微不足道的权利的触发清单
we're gonna save public and
我们将保存公众和
unfortunately there is no constructor
不幸的是，没有构造函数
injection
注射
you don't need strictly speaking this
你不需要严格地说这个
annotation if you're using public fields
注释（如果您使用的是公共字段）
as I am right now but if you decide to
就像我现在一样，但是如果你决定
do a private field which for some reason
做一个出于某种原因的私人领域
doesn't you know now that I've spent so
你现在不知道我已经花了
many years not doing it in spring night
很多年没有在春夜里这样做
I'd very much like to avoid private
我非常想避免私下
fields that that I can't get at - I
我无法获得的领域-我
can't influence through testing and
不能通过测试和
through collaborating objects that are
通过合作的对象是
passing through the constructor I'd very
通过构造函数我会非常
much like to avoid that so I'll just use
很想避免这种情况，所以我只用
public types instead so I'm public
而是公开类型，所以我是公开的
button
纽扣
but okay and finally I want to frost so
但是好吧，最后我想结霜
you know we have the initializing bean
你知道我们有初始化bean
callback interface in the spring well
春季的回调接口
same kind of principle applies after
同样的原则适用于
these have been bound by Java effects
这些都受到Java效果的约束
not by spring even though the bean
即使在春天之前
itself is being managed by spring after
春季之后
they were bound I want to build a
他们一定要建立一个
process and work with him so I'm going
和他一起工作，所以我要去
to say here this stuff button dot set
在这里说这个东西按钮点集
and on action listener and I'm given an
和动作监听器，我得到了一个
event and what I'm gonna do in the event
活动以及我在活动中要做的事情
is I'm just gonna well let's let's write
是我会很好，让我们写
some text
一些文字
okay so let's maybe let's nap let's
好吧，让我们也许小睡一下吧
announce in the label the look the
在标签中宣布外观
document base of the code in order to
该代码的文档库以
get the document base I need the
获取我需要的文档库
services and we already created those
服务，我们已经创建了这些
that pointer and earlier dinner man so
那个指针和早饭的人，所以
close services good and get document
关闭服务很好并获取文档
base alright alrighty good so there's
基本好吧好，所以有
that okay so there's our simple simple
好的，这就是我们的简单
demo you can see you know it's spring
演示，您可以看到春天
right this is all the stuff you like
对，这就是您喜欢的所有东西
this is gonna work this is gonna be
这将是工作，这将是
injected to spring lifecycle methods all
注入弹簧生命周期方法
that kind of stuff will be injected the
这种东西将被注入
only class is where you shouldn't be
唯一的课堂是你不应该去的地方
able to you know where you shouldn't
你能知道你不应该在哪里
take for granted the availability of
理所当然地认为
spring is this one right that's it
春天就是这样吗
everything else in this application is a
此应用程序中的其他所有内容都是
spring me until this is why I would just
让我开心，直到这就是为什么我会
get this right once and just not not not
一次正确地做到这一点，但不是没有
touch it you know just hide it somewhere
触摸它，你知道就把它藏在某个地方
we use it put in a jar it's a job okay
我们用它放在罐子里就可以了
um and what else do we want it let's say
嗯，我们还想要什么呢？
new runtime exception because we do have
新的运行时异常，因为我们确实有
a framework that can help us catch these
一个可以帮助我们捕捉到这些的框架
errors if there are any all right
如果有的话就报错
all right I think we're in a good place
好吧，我认为我们在一个好的地方
let's let's try it let's try it out huh
让我们尝试一下吧让我们尝试一下吧
so let's go ahead and run it
所以我们继续运行它
okay
好的
so there's a button if you click on it
所以有一个按钮，如果您单击它
it shows us the code base you know
它向我们展示了您所知道的代码库
location the actual document base I
定位实际文档库I
don't really you know we haven't even
真的不知道我们还没有
really begun to scratch the service here
真的开始在这里刮擦服务
we've got infinite number of things that
我们有无数的东西
we could do but I hopefully hopefully
我们可以做，但我希望
you've got you know an appreciation for
你已经知道了对
what's possible at this point right
在这一点上有什么可能
by using these things together we can
通过一起使用这些东西，我们可以
build user interfaces that are dynamic
建立动态的用户界面
that have tables and charts and grids
有表格，图表和网格
and so on and they can move quickly and
等等，他们可以快速移动，
they can support you know real-time sort
他们可以支持您了解实时排序
of 3d graphics and rendering and so you
3d图形和渲染等等
can do all sorts of really interesting
可以做各种非常有趣的事情
visualizations if nothing else consider
没有其他考虑的可视化
this as an as something to to power your
这是为您提供动力的一种方式
your observer ability sort of use cases
您的观察者能力用例
your goals your visualizations that kind
您的目标那种可视化
of thing there's a lot we haven't talked
事情很多，我们还没有谈过
about here obviously I wish I could have
大概在这里，我希望我可以
spent a little bit more time looking at
花了更多时间看
the web client over there or or indeed
那里的Web客户
technology technology is like our socket
技术就像我们的插座
right I mean you could use our socket to
对，我的意思是你可以用我们的插座
connect this to a back-end and that
将此连接到后端，
back-end of course would be powered by
后端当然会由
spring and you know the reactive web
春天，你知道反应网
framework or interactive spring with
框架或交互式弹簧
spring web plug so you can use our
弹簧网页插件，因此您可以使用我们的
socket or you can use web web services
套接字或您可以使用Web Web服务
HTTP REST API you can do whatever you
HTTP REST API，您可以做任何事情
want right in the backend but the
想要在后端，但
benefit is that we now have kind of a
好处是我们现在有一种
like-for-like experience on both client
在两个客户端上都有相同的经验
and service oh and of course this is
和服务哦，当然这是
spring so if you go to this spring boot
春天，所以如果你去这个 spring boot
build here configuration executive all
在这里建立配置执行程序
true and then you go to command line
true，然后转到命令行
the command line will go to the project
命令行将转到项目
itself CD downloads JavaFX doom even in
本身的CD即使在
package
包
well what did we get there
好，我们到那里去了
oh yeah my test doesn't see the post
哦，是的，我的测试没有看到该帖子
services so for now we'll just skip the
服务，所以现在我们就跳过
test that's an easy fix but that's tests
测试是一个简单的解决方法，但这是测试
all we have to do is to tell our test
我们要做的就是告诉我们的测试
free market that we have that those
自由市场，我们拥有那些
functional mean definitions which it
功能均值定义
doesn't see otherwise okay
否则看不到好
and we go to target and remember we have
我们去瞄准并记住我们有
a not just a an executive Oh fat jar
一个不只是高管哦胖子
right look at that we have that but you
正确的看，我们有那个，但是你
know what we have a we can just exact
知道我们有什么我们可以精确地
execute it like that right dot forward
像右点一样执行它
slash okay
斜线好吗
there we go all right my friends thanks
在那里，我们一切顺利，我的朋友们，谢谢
so much for watching and we'll see
这么多的观看，我们会看到
you
您